Scientist
Hello Hello Friends Welcome to my channel
Sweater
Interested of SCI Monday General
Insurance Current Market Price is to be added on
Star Plus 1498
[Music]
Target till daily 600 800 60
60 60
seven
as you have
subscribed from here done
more
06 and it is moving up by one and a half inch till here it is
taking support at 1597
and 1497 before also Jacintha put it here in it
crosses this
scandal, it has relabeled
you 307 so the whole 9798 is a nice flower
so it is inside to wish with a stoploss at 1490
we will enter the
comment line on wanderer for years and
as you can see it is
banked with volume see this green card and green candle
now we have banked with average volume here here here so it was
beaten like this
now the second one it will come to test completely
4097 you can rebel this trade line in it
below incomplete there is
no need to worry if we
can reach 5105 we can play for this target inside it ok khodi
explain it happened
to Ajay
that indigo indigo on Friday and
mother entered in my personal account something about
cases oh as you can see there is
a thick eat above in it that in
these days this feeling has happened,
this blue bridge has been set up with volume
that this weekend to check it
out you can see here now this
area here this area had given a
breakout
around this level it had
given a back vote 80 you can take it from here
9084 is in demand there is a lot of it here after leaving it I
cut the spray with snake volume
and
we can take it to 150 1958 Africa
I did a few points here and if it goes
down then I will put some quantity here at
2075 level and 850  The
stoploss level of 83830 below is a problem
because son, you will have to
keep a little bit of dry ginger in it, the
returns are good, its target will be
2031 for
Loot,
next on 9 06, on
6 October, it was decided
that these will be our Tigers, 214 six and
last one two two two
interest play, so definitely he has a
bank account, so he
came to test without pregnancy, from below a
little above Mr. Rajesh, where is the target 1000,
which should be quiet as it is,
if we look at the famous chart, then
on the weekly chart, the
slashed shoulder had given all the records,
Ajay, the
head of Loot, has spread his
grinding around Gautam, how has he
given breakfast, there is
no need to worry, it is soft inside, anyway,
you will move the stock industries like this, on the
Tata Sons, the news of Air India, if a
little bit of silver leader is found below anywhere
on Monday, it is good that it will be seen
below at this level, on the strength of this, you can see that the
support of the first good  How much will it give,
I will get this level done, after that
he is jogging, he
can also wear something at the level of 12345,
click on the like button and below this we will be
able to put a stoploss below this line, by the way,
its okay, we will play Inter Arts
and Electronics in Apollo Hospital,
I
said, you can see like a movie, without
volume, it is being set here and one
thing, this rule of 4370 room
rent which I had written on Airtel account, I had done it earlier as
well, I would have made it reach from there to
president level, you are my kurti position, there is
more tension in this, this forces, if it stands below this for
two to three hours, then
we will add it to it, then we will go to
test the photo to photo 1021 inch level below us,
okay, the
rest of the forces have come in it on Friday also, let's
see, the character of 4705 is
our stoploss, the rest close
investor will see what is there or not,
press this target once, its Arya, its
started  For this we will play
its plain crash critical at 4905 91512,
after that we will target it and
take forces, first we will see tomorrow whether it does
satsang at this level of 14370 or not,
if it does not stand then we will
unite it, then we will enter inside it
on the labels of the software, okay,
I will tell you that first see in it whether it does
setting for 40 only or not,
next of the Hindustan Unilever is
that
inside Hindustan Unilever you can see
how
here in this area,
breakup record was given,
after a long time at 2612 level, specific was given and here
taking 2532,
2532 level
66, if this is next
2532, there is bring to front, these
six
questions
come, so
you will
get their strength, target of 2017 scope,
educated
2686 500
6270, you will have to
watch tomorrow's show of T20, Hindustan
Unilever  Is it touching the 2017 level or
not? If it had
stood above the seven for an hour or two, then we would have
greased the interlink with a small stop loss and the new news policy of this level,
then we will take entry here at the level of 2532,
okay, it is clear, this has been discussed.
[Music]
Next 9
Ajay
[Music]
New Delhi India, now you see
that this is here, this tree
of Riding Gautam was broken, if you see here
80,
Redmi Note 4 only loves and
hates, it does
not do anything above this, if it does not
do anything then something here and S&P 500
600 800
to
[Music]
200 1967 Utpat
9769,
a little
12% NH 28
Jhaal
scientist, we will take secondary, in this from eight
to ground,
if we get you problem on top 10,
zinc waste from Friday, okay,
so that cigarettes
are there and
[Music]
2015 ad PCMC
And tell me, there was a
Jhala
loot like this, you can see that like it happened,
Ajay was
looted at
26, its support is being lost, this
lead is being
watched from Tubelight at 123 level,
and if someone does
not want to take risk in this, then send it to 2954 2.5 level,
then target of Dhaniya proper,
this is his job, lingerie, Veena, this app is for
filler problem,
apart from this, 60 60 60, lawyer for NAPA, 12351,
head
loot, 3128
3152,
okay, so let's
see 200 more songs and torque,
Indian Bank is
Jhala
loot,
that these were, if we show you, then
this section area has been made, indicator ahead of
1127, upside-down side, which level of Adams is
1103, and a cup has been given, world
recovery has been given on this, as soon as we have to
take the indication, as soon as it
stands on 11-09-2012 powder above it  When he comes,
his mouth will be very fast, it
crosses 2010,
put your 4000 with the volume, let's put the date, he gets this
stan, then one enter
volume satsang,
gegli.com will give movement, then Jhaal Indian
leg, then you
can take the time of 2017, independent
end,
Jhaal Ajay, rest if it was for Akshar, then I would show it
on the television channel,
please like, share and subscribe to the channel
which is born and
thank you for a
show more